FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
YEAR 2026
Now,
everyone, let's raise a glass to
our artist, who gave us such a wonderful
performance today.
Congratulations are also in order…
To Jae-in on this first step as Pi-o's
new manager.
I'm glad everything wrapped up without
issue.
Still,
do you have any idea how
much you scared me?
You took ten years off of my life.
We all owe it to Jae-in, of course.
You know…
knowing you're Pi-o's manager gives
me so much peace of mind.
You don't have to tell me how tough
it must be.
- I feel bad for you.
- You're not wrong
Ms. Kang.
I only put up with it cos I'm a big fan.
Ufff…
Honestly,
how many people get to make money with
their favorite thing?
Know what I mean?
That's how I cope.
Still,
if he ever gives me a real hard time,
you'll scold him for me, won't you?
Of course.
How's the Esplanade show coming along?
All seats are completely sold out,
but there are additional requests for
VIP tickets,
so we're negotiating with the Singapore
agency.
Sorry, Excuse me for a moment.
Okay.
The time between the Vienna and Singapore
concerts is too tight.
- Sorry 'bout that.
- Kang Pi-o?
Hey, it's really you!
Been a while.
I've seen you on the news from
time to time.
You know how I've been up to, right?
What's up with that rumor about Choi
Jeong-yo?
What exactly happened with that?
I heard that you had something to do with
it.
I see you're just as pathetic as you were
back in school.
What?
Since when has your pinky been like this?
If you leave it like that, you're
gonna ruin it.
Stop practicing and get it treated first.
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
EPISODE 6
Mm
Guess where I am.
Turn around.
PI-O PI-O
Ta-da.
Ah…
This is nice.
I wonder…
Why is it that I never get tired of
listening to you?
You have no idea…
how glad I am that I became your manager.
Can you stop saying things like that?
It's not funny.
What do you mean?
How many people out there get to hear…
a million-dollar performance
without having to fight for a ticket
to the show?
Hey,
be honest with me.
You actually…
really like having me as your mm-manager,
don't you?
- I do, yeah.
- You actually like it when I drop in…
without telling you first, right?
I do.
Then,
when are we getting married?
I--
Wow, aren't you tired of asking me that?
Hey!
Haven't I done enough
to win you over by now?
Hey, you're not gonna brush me off by
saying you're married to your music,
- are you?
- Oh, hey you figured it out.
Ugh, What do I even see in him…
Hey, wait up!
Hurry.
Now, let's ask some questions to the
star of this competition,
and the most renowned pianist,
Mister Pi-o Kang!
Woot woot woot!
Ever since the Harmonie Competition
nine years ago,
you've been at the forefront of bringing
classical music to a wider audience
with both undeniable skill and star
quality!
Back then,
you shocked everyone by
delivering an explosive
performance even after breaking a nail.
How did you do it?
Back then,
I was focused, so…
I didn't feel any pain at all.
The Harmonie Competition was a stage
I dreamed of performing upon.
And once I was there,
pain in my finger didn't matter.
Wow.
What was even more astonishing was your
unique interpretation of the set piece.
To make an interpretation like that and
deliver such a complete performance
in just a week is no small achievement.
How were you able to accomplish such a
difficult challenge?
It definitely wasn't easy.
The pressure was intense.
I just focused on doing the best,
and it led to a good result.
I don't know if I could ever pull that
off again.
Okay, now that nine years have
passed, I'd like to ask you a more
sensitive question.
At the time, the finalists must have been
deeply shaken by the loss of a fellow
competitor.
It remains an unhealed wound for
us on the committee as well.
How did you overcome that?
Uh…
Um… It's been a very long time, but
life goes on
and music
heals us all, right?
For me,
music was my healing and my salvation.
Come to think of it,
you went to the same school as that
competitor, right?
- Yes.
- Were you close?
Uh-- No, we weren't that close.
Good job out there, Kang Pi-o!
These are yours.
Gifts from your fans in Korea.
They go all out, don't they?
MESSAGES
NEW NOTIFICATION
I found someone who says he spotted Mr.
Choi in Romania.
Jae-in.
- Excuse me…
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, Mister Kang.
All right, tell me everything.
Who is this guy you found?
Ah, well,
his name is Farid and he's a refugee.
When I asked if he knew where Mister Choi
went,
he demanded money for the info. So?
- Should I pay him and see what he knows?
- Not yet.
I'd like to go over there
and verify it myself.
Oh…
Let's go.
Oh… I can't come to the party tonight.
Why not?
You said you'd come though.
Don't make me go alone.
I'm sorry, it's just…
A professor I've been wanting to
meet for a while said he has some
time for me tomorrow.
But, I'll need to go to Münster.
Hm…
Guess it can't be helped.
The promo party, though…
You can't miss.
We really need you there for that one.
I know you do. Back soon, 'kay?
Václav Havel Airport, please.
Honey,
MOM
AS FOR ME, I GOT THE COMMITTEE
POSITION I MENTIONED THE OTHER DAY
Smile when you take a bow.
IT'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE QUITE A HASSLE
You're not sick, are you?
We will now begin the appointment
ceremony for new members of the National
Culture and Arts Promotion Fund Steering
Committee.
SHAPING THE FUTURE
THROUGH CULTURE AND ARTS
You are hereby appointed as a member of
the Music Division of the National
LOCATION: MAIN AUDITORIUM,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, AND TOURISM
Kim Tae-seong, Minister of
Culture, Sports, and Tourism.
Seriously, You're unbelievable!
How did you manage to beat everyone else
and snag a seat on the committee so
quickly?
I admire you…
and not just cos we're friends.
Oh, you're just saying that.
I only got cos it was my turn.
So, Ms. Committee Member,
what's on your agenda?
Oh, my duties start next week.
Today,
I'm just helping evaluate the
gifted school admissions.
Really?
Have you see any candidates there worth
recommending?
I'm still a bit bitter…
that Namu Productions got Park Sae-jin.
I'll have to see how he does today.
How about Gam U-jin?
He seems pretty good.
Oh, Gam U-jin?
What? You don't like him?
Oh, I know he's talented,
His looks, though…
Hey, you need to pick a kid with
musical talent
if you want an artist who can win
awards, I mean
they're not actors.
That's not how it works.
A handsome kid,
will sell tickets even if
their hands shake on stage.
Music is eighty percent about looks.
All right then, I'll let you know if
there's a decent candidate there today,
just hang tight.
Oh, you know I love you, right?
I swear, what would I do without you?
Ah, stop it.
I'll call you later, 'kay?
Mrs. Kim!
I think the dry cleaners made a mistake.
These clothes aren't mine.
Oh, these are Ms. Yoon's old--
Oh…
Why haven't you gotten rid of the
clothes of someone who left this
house five years ago?
And of all places…
Why would you hang them in my room?
Well…
I would've taken them out if I'd known.
Perhaps, Ms. Lee…
noticed them in Mister Kang's room
and mistook them for yours, and hung them
there.
Throw them out immediately.
As for me, Hyeon Seon-hwa, Lee Na-rae,
2026 CHEONGUN MUSIC EDUCATION
APPLICATION FORM
and Gam U-jin, look good.
Uh, I think these three show the most
potential.
And of the three, Gam U-jin seems, uh…
to most closely fit the profile
of the type of student we are looking
for.
Excuse me.
You said Gam U-jin - was your favorite?
I don't know about him.
He's a bit of a gamble.
I know he seems very talented, but his
fundamentals are lacking.
It's just…
I worry he'll put style over substance.
He makes mistakes because he started
playing later than the others, which
is to be expected.
And if we want - to find a prodigy
shouldn't we look at their potential
rather than the superficial aspects?
Superficial, you say?
Surely you know how crucial the
first year or two are in a young
musician's development.
Why should a taxpayer-funded institute
like ours…
waste resources on a kid whose
fingers have already stiffened?
I propose… rather than Gam U-jin…
This one. Kim Hong-gyu.
I'd put them forward instead.
Hyun-soo!
What was with that look all about?
What?
Did you not like the candidate I put
forward?
No, I didn't like him.
Is it right to let our history
influence a decision that'll affect a
- child's future?
- What are you talking about?
What,
do you actually think that I rejected
Gam U-jin just to pick a fight with you?
You're right.
I wanted to see what your
reaction would be like.
And that's what it took,
to get you to talk to me.
How long will you treat me like this?
Isn't it crazy,
that we only ended up like this, because…
- somebody else got between us?
- No,
it wasn't because of someone else.
It's your fault we're like this.
Enough.
ROMANIA
Ah! Hello.
- May I help you?
- Ah, sorry.
Ah…
I've a question.
Um…
Let's see now…
Uh… Mister Farid.
Mm-hmm.
You mentioned that three years ago,
you encountered another homeless man
who played the piano well, right?
Yeah. That's right.
Yes, he says he did.
Could you identify
which of these men he was?
Mmm
Uh… This man here.
How did you know
he was good at playing the piano?
Did you see him play yourself?
Um…
He said, um…
his dream was to be a pianist,
but…
- he was heartbroken that he could
- He says the man dreamt of being a
- no longer pursue that dream.
- pianist, but was heartbroken as he
- Because he couldn't use his right
- couldn't pursue it.
Hand anymore…
he couldn't use his right hand anymore.
H- he couldn't use his
right hand anymore?
Did he say why he couldn't use it?
Why couldn't he use his right hand?
Do you know why?
Uh…
He just said
that he had hurt it.
- He didn't say how he'd gotten hurt.
- Some kind of an injury,
but he didn't tell him how it happened.
Do you know where he went after you
saw him?
Where did he go after that?
Uh… Um, I'm sorry, but…
I'm gonna need… A hit pretty soon.
Could I have some money?
He needs cash for his drug habit.
I want you to be specific.
Where did he say he was going?
He want's you to be specific.
Do you know where he might have gone?
He said he was…
gonna board a ship…
and return to his hometown or something.
He said… he was going to Constanța.
He said he caught a ship to return to
his hometown.
He said he missed his mom, that she
was waiting for him to come home.
Said he missed his mom.
He mentioned…
going to see his mom?
You're looking for the pianist.
He hasn't been here for two weeks.
But, I saw him two weeks ago, Yeah,
he was definitely here.
This guy…? No - this one's not him.
But… this guy.
He was here.
This man. He was here.
This is him.
That man was Korean,
but he wasn't a pianist.
What is he saying?
That the man was Korean,
but not a pianist.
How much longer are we gonna
keep shooting in the dark like this?
It's been five years already.
After all this time,
shouldn't you have at least
found a clue by now?
It's not like I'm asking you to catch the
kidnappers.
I just wanna know if he's dead or not.
Is it really that hard?
Look, even Interpol couldn't locate him.
You think it's easy for me?
What then? Do you… wanna stop looking?
Look, my reputations on the line
too, 'kay?
I mean, Interpol has already concluded
that Mister Choi is dead.
And we've searched everywhere we
could think of.
The only thing we haven't
found is his body.
Mister Choi's chances of being alive
are next to zero.
What exactly is it that you want to
confirm?
Is it that Mr. Choi is alive?
Or that he is dead?
- Cheers!
- Here's to us!
What exactly is it that you want to
confirm?
Is it that Mr. Choi is alive?
Or that he is dead?
- Mm?
- Hey,
where are you?
The party's over and you even
didn't show.
Oh, sorry.
Guess I forgot.
Have you been drinking?
A little…
Where are you right now?
Ugh…
Hey, Kang Pi-o!
Hey wake up.
What's going on?
Oh…
You're here.
Um… Did something happen?
Why did you drink so many beers all
on your own?
Nothing happened.
Hey
Hey… Pi-O!! Careful!
Seriously,
What the hell's gotten into you?
- Ugh…
- Keep walking.
- Okay?
We're almost there.
- Ugh…
- Oh…
No. I'm fine.
You can go.
I can walk on my own.
You're going to get hurt.
Where's your key?
Jae-in.
I'm sorry.
Could you please just stay with me
until I fall asleep?
What?
You won't even accept how I feel,
but still want me to watch you
fall asleep?
You're so selfish.
Because you're the only one…
that I can trust.
Yeah, I know.
Do you still have a lot of trouble
sleeping?
Mm-hmm.
I just want to clear my head
and sleep for a while.
I told you to stop working so hard.
You need to get some rest.
How about cutting some of your shows?
You could take a sabbatical.
How's that?
Maybe.
Give yourself a break.
Just relax
You're doing a great job.
Pi-o.
I'd like to get something off my chest.
Can I?
Sure…
Well, it's just that…
You know that I really like you a lot,
right?
You know, right?
I know.
No, you don't.
You have no idea.
The truth is…
Every time I told you…
I made it sound like I was joking
and laughed it off…
but actually, I meant every word.
Just don't be in pain, Kang Pi-o.
I found out the man who kidnapped
Mister Choi was just released from
Rezina Penitentiary.
What did you mean with that text?
You mean you know where he is?
MOLDOVA
His name is Andrei Ceban.
He's from Transnistria.
He's forty-eight.
A former mercenary.
He was serving time for assault.
They just let him out.
Man, no wonder I couldn't find a trace of
him, the bastard was locked up.
By the way, can I ask you something?
Ah, you told me not to ask any questions,
so I haven't…
But Mister Kang,
why are you trying so hard to find Mister
Choi?
Even his family would've given up.
Is he really all that important to you?
This Mister Choi?
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Where are you going?
Oh, uh, Andrei Ceban here?
- And your name?
- Ah, Vogel.
Ah, that guy. Inside.
- Wait a moment.
- Okay.
Mm.
Okay?
Hey!
Ah, uh…
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Andrei.
I hope you don't mind…
if we ask you a few questions.
just sit down!
Nine years ago,
at the Harmonie Competition.
Are you the one who abducted this man?
Who the hell's asking?
Oh…
I remember you.
You're the guy who won that competition,
right?
The one who benefited the most from that…
mess.
Let me ask you again.
You abducted Jeong-yo Choi, right?
What's in it for me?
What did you do
to Jeong-yo?
He's dead.
- Dead?
- Yes, dead.
- By whom?
- Me.
Why did you kill him?
Why… did you kill him?
It was not the plan.
The plan was to let him go after
we got the money.
But…
he put up a bit too much of a fight.
Was it for money?
Did you abduct him for that reason?
Or did someone--
Enough.
You want to know?
Three million lei.
Then I'll tell you.
- Tell me!
- Mister Kang, don't!
You killed him for something so small?
You know who he was? He was my friend!
Come on, stop!
Do you know who we are?
You little…
Huh?
You know what?
Now,
six million.
Then I'll tell you.
Ugh…
Is there an international bank close
by here?
Huh? You wanna come back?
Huh? Hold up.
What's going on?
Crap…
Excuse me sir, you can’t come in here.
POLICE
A man named Andrei has been killed.
Some kind of a fight.
He tell you what happened?
Andrei, uh…
was just murdered.
- I don't understand.
- Apparently there was some kind of fight…
and he was killed.
- No.
- Wait, Pi-o.
Wait, don't be stupid!
Wait! Pi-o, don't…!
Hey…
Stop, Stop Pi-o!
Are you all right?
Ah, guess my work here's done.
I'm sure that Mister Choi is, uh…
looking down from heaven with a smile.
Knowing he had a friend
who spent all this time searching
for him.
Now that it's done…
I hope you can let go of the dead.
And find some happiness.
Thank you for everything.
Hey, Kang Pi-o!
Where did you go?
How come your not back yet?
You said you'd make time for U-hyeok,
but you haven't.
Anyway, guess what?
He made it to the semifinals.
Where are you? You back in Berlin?
No.
I'm in Moldova…
What?
Moldova?
Uh…
What's wrong with your voice, you okay?
Are you sick?
Kang Pi-o!
Hey…
You can't just stay in bed like this.
You need a doctor…
I need a headache pill…
- Huh?
- I just need a headache pill.
That's it?
Okay.
Are you feeling better now?
Uh-huh…
Good…
I brought you a little something to
eat as well.
It doesn't look very good, but…
you should eat.
Even just a little bit.
It'll give you some energy.
Thanks.
Sorry.
Really
So, uh…
Wanna share?
What were you doing all the way out here?
Uh…
is there something you're hiding from me?
I came here hoping to meet Jeong-yo.
Huh?
I heard that the guy who kidnapped him,
Got out of jail and was living here.
And then?
Jeong-yo's dead.
He's been dead since that day.
Nine years ago.
I was hoping he was still alive.
I hoped…
I had really hoped that he wasn't dead.
Now there's no way I'll be forgiven.
There's no going back.
It's time for you to move on.
I mean, it happened so long ago. So why…
Because I stole Jeong-yo's spot-light.
Oh, why would you say something
like that, huh?
You played really well that night.
That's why no-one ever questioned
the judges decision.
Even if Jeong-yo had played…
you would've won.
No.
I'm sitting in Jeong-yo's spot.
And now…
I can't even set things right anymore.
Why didn't you tell me?
If you were hurting…
Why didn't you at least tell me?
Just let it go… Pi-o.
We should…
just let Jeong-yo go.
I believe…
that's what Jeong-yo would want.
He would want you…
to become an amazing
pianist in his place.
I promise I will never leave you.
Your plane's leaving soon.
Don't go crying just cos you miss me.
Hey.
You really gonna keep making me feel this
is one-sided?
I'll get going.
Mm-hmm.
Bye.
Hey, kiddo!
Here. I got it.
I told you not to come pick me up,
why are you here?
How could I not?
I haven't seen you in six months, right?
I miss you so much I cried.
I saw the video of your gala in Prague.
You were great.
Your Berlin Concert?
How was it?
Fine.
Hey. Let me take that.
Welcome home, Pi-o.
I hope you've been well.
His luggage is in the trunk. Could you
get it?
Where's Mister Kang?
Father.
Pi-o is here.
Hello Grandfather… how've you been?
Your one and only grandson is back after
six months.
Could you say something to him?
You're in the way.
Can you move? You're blocking my fan.
Oh…
Let's go.
He's a stubborn old man.
I thought he'd get better when he got
older…
but he's just as stubborn as ever.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine with it.
PRAGUE HARMONIE INTERNATIONAL COMPETITION
I'VE ALREADY MEMORIZED IT ALL
USE IT IF YOU NEED IT!
Hi, Pi-o!
Have you been well, Ms. Han?
I haven't been well, because I
missed you.
Going to see your performances was the
highlight of my days,
but I've been too busy for that.
Hey… You're looking a bit pale.
Is something the matter?
Not at all.
Look, your album's out.
What do you think?
Came out nicely, right?
Mm
We should start planning your recital
tour to coincide with the album's
release.
Pi-o, what cities do you want to play?
Well,
the usual ones.
Hmm…
So, at minimum, Seoul, Incheon,
Daejeon, Daegu, Busan,
and Tongyeong.
I think that'll be a nice tour.
You agree? Too many at once?
Should we just do four cities?
No, it's good.
It should be fine.
LEDANOL
Pi-o.
KANG PI-O, GENIUS ON THE BRINK?
FIRST CRACK IN THE PERFECTIONIST'S ARMOR
A MYSTERIOUS REPEATED PASSAGE
WHILE PERFORMING "GASPARD DE LA NUIT"…
Please just open this door.
You haven't eaten anything in days!
You've had so many event's lately and
you couldn't practice.
You're just under the weather, that's all
it is.
Just rest up.
You're routine will help you back-- Oh…
Pi…
Pi-o.
Mr. Do.
I'm all messed up…
And you still…
can't stand to see my face?
I waited for you for so long…
and you avoid me?
Why?
Are you uncomfortable around me now cos
of my mom, or is it something else?
Is it because I was never a good enough
student for you?
What are you talking about? That's not
true.
No, uh…
Can you… Just be honest with me.
Did you ever really consider me
your student, Mister Do?
Pi-o, what are you talking about?
I've always, uh…
wanted to ask you this.
Why did you make me play the same piece
as Jeong-yo?
What?
I told you that I wanted to play Rach
Three, so why did you make me play
Rach Two?
Did you do that to me on purpose?
So everyone could see how much
better he was?
Pi-o, I'm afraid that's a terrible
misunderstanding.
Both you and Jeong-yo
were equally precious.
Both of you were so important to me.
Then why is it you're always giving me
such a cold shoulder?
You know I've always counted on your
guidance and your help, so… why…
Why is there only room in your heart
for the one who's gone?
No. That's not true.
My heart breaks for you, too.
And I'm worried.
But, now, there's really nothing left
for me to teach you
because you've become a pianist
with a voice of your own.
I thought the best thing I could do was…
to quietly cheer you
on from the sidelines.
That's not true!
You've always hated me!
Hey, just admit that I'm a student
that you never wanted!
You know I'm an amateur hack and have
ZERO talent!
Say you couldn't stand having
a pathetic student…
who played music without ANY SOUL!
Ah…
KANG PI-O RECITAL
THE CRACKS DIDN'T START ON STAGE
PIANIST KANG PI-O'S DOWNFALL
WAS INEVITABLE
Kang Pi-o, get up, now.
Jae-in's here, so get up.
I said you have a guest-
Pi-o.
Come on, sit up here.
So…
How long are you going
to keep doing this?
So you ruined one show - Is your life
finished?
The deeper you let yourself sink,
the harder it is to find the
surface again, right?
I'm sorry…
Just leave me alone.
I'll be fine on my own.
Look, instead of staying here in Korea,
why don't you go travel somewhere?
I know it's harder for you to stay here
with all the rumors, the prying eyes,
and everything else.
Take that trip around Europe
you've always wanted to do.
It might help clear your head.
Where am I going to hide?
Nothing changes the fact I can't play the
piano.
There's nowhere I can hide from it.
LEE BO-HUN
I kept seeing what looked like the ghost
of---
my missing friend.
I thought that if I held some kind of
funeral for him,
I'd finally get better.
But now I feel like…
I'm sinking under water…
Cos I know he's dead.
Uh, maybe
it's because you never gave yourself the
time to properly mourn him.
Hm, perhaps…
you could take a little time to properly
face your grief?
Accepting it…
and letting it go is the best way to move
forward.
Yeah me too.
Should we go inside?
Yeah, let's find our seats.
SPECIAL THANKS TO KO CHANG-SEOK
FOR HIS GUEST APPEARANCE
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
Today's winner, Luca Domenico.
Choi Jeong-yo has returned.
I do not wish for my music to be…
overshadowed by my past.
There's no way I wouldn't recognize you.
It's definitely Jeong-yo.
Choi Jeong-yo! Please, let me see him.
Mr. Domenico says he doesn't know you.
I have another favor to ask.
GENERATIVE AI TECHNOLOGY
WAS USED IN SOME SCENES.
Look into it.
Dig into it without anyone finding out.